Lesson 30. The death of a ghost. For years, villagers believed that Endley farm was hunted.
第30课。幽灵的死亡。多年来，村民们认为恩德利农场被猎杀。
The farm was owned by two brothers. Joe and Bob Cox, they employed a few farm hands.
该农场由两个兄弟拥有。乔和鲍勃·考克斯（Joe and Bob Cox）雇用了几只农场手。
But no one was willing to work there long. Every time a worker gave up his job, he told the same
但是没有人愿意在那里工作很长时间。每当工人放弃工作时，他都告诉
overnight: adv. 一夜期间
story. Farm laborers said that they always woke up to find that work had been done overnight.
故事。农场工人说，他们总是醒来发现工作已经在一夜之间完成。
He had been cut and cow sheds had been cleaned. A farm worker, who stayed up all night,
他被切断了，牛棚已经清洗了。一个整夜熬夜的农场工人
corn: n.   谷物, moonlight: n.   月光
claimed to have seen a figure cutting corn in the moonlight. In time, it became an accepted fact
声称已经看到了一个人物在月光中砍伐玉米。随着时间的流逝，这成为一个公认的事实
conscientious: adj. 认真的
the Cox brothers employed a conscientious ghost that did most of their work for them.
考克斯兄弟（Cox Brothers）采用了一个认真的幽灵，为他们做了大部分工作。
suspect: v.   怀疑
No one suspected that there might be someone else on the farm who had never been seen.
没有人怀疑农场上可能有其他人从未见过。
This was indeed the case. A short time ago, villagers were astonished to learn that the ghost
确实就是这样。不久前，村民们惊讶地得知鬼魂
of Endley had died. Everyone went to the funeral. For the ghost, was none other than Eric Cox.
恩德利（Endley）死了。每个人都参加了葬礼。对于幽灵，就是埃里克·考克斯（Eric Cox）。
A third brother who was supposed to have died as a young man. After the funeral,
本应年轻时去世的第三个兄弟。葬礼之后，
Joe and Bob revealed a secret which they had kept for over 50 years.
乔和鲍勃（Joe and Bob）透露了他们保留了50多年的秘密。
Eric had been the eldest son of the family. Very much older than his two brothers. He had been
埃里克（Eric）曾是家庭的长子。比他的两个兄弟大得多。他曾经
desert: v.   （军队中）开小差
obliged to join the army during the Second World War. As he hated army life, he decided to desert
在第二次世界大战期间不得不参加军队。当他讨厌陆军生活时，他决定抛弃
regiment: n.   （军队）团
his regiment. When he learnt that he would be sent abroad, he returned to the farm and his father
他的团。当他得知自己将被送到国外时，他回到了农场和父亲
hid him until the end of the war. Fearing the authorities, Eric remained in hiding after the war
把他藏起来直到战争结束。担心当局，埃里克（Eric）留在战后躲藏起来
action: n.   战斗
as well. His father told everybody that Eric had been killed in action. The only other people who
也他的父亲告诉所有人，埃里克（Eric）在行动中被杀。唯一的其他人
knew the secret were Joe and Bob. They did not even tell their wives. When their father died,
知道秘密是乔和鲍勃。他们甚至没有告诉妻子。当他们父亲去世时
recluse: n.   隐士
they thought it their duty to keep Eric in hiding. All these years, Eric had lived as a recluse.
他们认为让埃里克躲藏起来是他们的责任。这些年来，埃里克（Eric）一直是一个隐士。
He used to sleep during the day and work at night, quite unaware of the fact that he had become
他曾经白天睡觉，晚上工作，这不知道他已经成为
the ghost of Endley. When he died, however, his brothers found it impossible to keep the secret any longer.
恩德利的幽灵。然而，当他去世时，他的兄弟们发现不再保留秘密。